Wait a moment, wait a moment, he will give the signal, and he will be included. Are you signaling like this? If you are a fan,
Hit it, hit it, hit it, hit it! He is a fan, so are the Red Wolves your teammate? Is this your teammate?
Try it, you go ahead. You red wolf gave me a signal and hit me on the head.
Were you accidentally injured just now? Red Wolf, were you accidentally injured? If you are, just nod.
Oh, it was a mistake, it was a mistake. OK, OK, OK, OK, you pick up the gun first, pick up the gun, pick up the gun!
You picked up the gun. Red Wolf, Weilong and Birdman, you three come over and have a meeting, have a meeting,
Have a meeting! Let’s give these bags first, they are mine and my current teammates can eat them.
Because he and his teammates met me all the time,
Just give them what you just licked. I'll take you to eat later. OK,
Bao, nod if it’s okay. OK, OK, after the meeting, ask me to open a card for the three of them. red wolf,
You go and eat this, Red Wolf, you go and eat it.
No, that’s not what it is? Are you going to eat? Are you a demon? Holy shit! Oops,
It’s so fun to play games and meet teammates, brothers, it’s really fun! hello,
Hello, hello, come on, I'm waiting, what about the red wolf?
Red Wolf said that the two of us would fight first because we were together. The red wolf was part of our wild platoon at that time.
Then I'll take him alone for a while, okay?
Okay, do you want to attack with me, or do you want to fight with you? Fight together, fight together,
No? Yes, fight together, fight together? Look at our two equipments, holy shit! OK, OK,
Okay, okay, let’s go, let’s go! Hey, I’m so nervous! It's okay, it's okay, I talk much better usually,
Today I suddenly don’t know what to say and am nervous. Oops, get out of here! I'm not nervous,
If you're nervous, don't take me with you! Let’s look at the third one, anchor, let’s play the second pass together, it doesn’t matter.
Veteran, good gun, good gun, good gun! One short pile, another pile, pour one, pour one, what a gun!
Anyway, it’s just one, let’s go, let’s go! Ah, people are coming out of Welfare, people are coming out of Welfare! Damn it, stop the car,
Stop the car!
This boss is so strong! Come on, come on, come on! I run the red and blue slide shovel sniper. I used to slide slide sniper.
So are you truly a king? Isn’t this you? How did you learn it? Oops,
I learned this all from watching your live broadcast. No, no, my live broadcast, you oops!
Let me tell you, when I hit you, anchor, my hands were weak.
I took a dozen and added them to yours, and then he said that it would become a big king, and then it would become soft after just one dozen.
Did you know? Ha ha ha ha! oops! Gee, this is so boring! You are so crazy,
I never saw you so crazy before today. Look at your potential, little brother! Hey,
What's your girlfriend's name? Don't go! Xiaoguo, Xiaoguo, oh, Xiaoguo, yes,
I know dog, not dog, not dog, OK, OK, two yes.
So cute! This one won’t let the host step on landmines. If you want to step on it, I’ll step on it first, okay? Do you step on it first?
No, no, no, it’s okay, I’ll step on it first. Come on, I'm going to fuck my teammates, wait a minute! Oh, Feng Yi, I'll come,
Here I come! Oops, there's nothing left, brother! Well, come on, do I see it? And teammates,
And teammates! Here, here, here, here! I took a few shots.
Die, die, die! oops! Hey, hey, hey, don’t, don’t, don’t, don’t, don’t, don’t! I'll get it! OK,
OK, wow, time flies so fast! Yes, that habit is so big, so happy! OK,
Okay, how much does it cost? Our purpose is not to eat, you know that right? That's right,
The main one is playing games! Yeah? oops! Yes, Yes, Yes, Yes.